Solza Motorsports
Now that we have introduced with us
Forza Motorsports has finally been launched!
It's right in front of your eyes, isn't it?
The game's play screen.
It's hard to tell when you look at it from a close-up.
It's just the monitor.
But it's right in front of our eyes.
Do you both remember the theme of this game?
Seino
Falling in love with car
That's what "Se-no" means.
That's exactly what it means.
Falling in love with cars.
You choose your car and you play.
Romantic.
It's an easy theme to understand.
What is it? Kokoro.
She said "together.
Together, you mean.
That's what I meant.
That's what I mean.
Today is the launch of Forza Motorsport.
We're going to actually play it.
Yay!
By the way, last time in this program, we did a coloring book.
You designed a car, didn't you?You designed the car.
Do you remember that?
Yes, I remember.
Do you remember what kind of design you did? Yuno...
The light green is intense.
It's so easy on the eyes.
I didn't expect it, since I had a green bag last time.
The car won't show through.
It won't show through the car.
Remember me, Rei?
You got in with 007, didn't you?
This is the best.
The car design.
I put it on the front of the car.
I'm not sure what to do with it today.
It's really hard to decide.
Do I go with pink or this?
You know, the show was an inspiration for me.
I started to look at sports cars on the street
I started to look at the color of the car.
That's a good thing.
For design reference.
I've never seen pink before.
That's true.
There's usually bright red, right?
Red, yellow, matte...
That's what most of them are.
That makes pink a bit of a problem.
It's unique, isn't it?
Yes, but in the game, you can make it happen.Yeah, yeah, but we can make it happen in the game.
Because it's in the game
I'm sure there are some colors that would look better in a game.
What about you, Maya?
I'd like to have a character that looks like me in the game.
I'd like to have a character that looks like me
I'd like to have a character that looks like me.
I'm a bit of a nerd, so to speak.
It's called itasha.
I designed it to look like
but
I put the name "Rikamayama" on it.
I put the logo
The "A" didn't fit.
Rikamaya
RIKAMAYA
So...
Maybe we can put the A in today?
Today.
I'd like to do it today.
I'd like to get in today.
I don't think it'll be like that coloring book.
I don't think it'll be irreversible.
You can do it over and over again.
I think I can customize it as much as I want.
Today, in fact.
Let's customize your own car in the game.
Yes, sir.
Let's customize each car.Let's go ahead and customize each of these cars.
Let's customize each car.
I have a Honda Civic Type R.
I am.
I had a Subaru STI.
And you?
I have a Ford Mustang GT.
It's so cool!
You're gonna post the price, too?
We'll get the price too.
Where? Where?
It's right there.
Oh, my God, it's true.
Eighty-eight thousand.
88,000?
Point-wise.
89,000.
89,000?
83,000?
That's kind of low.
I don't know why.
I don't know.
Well, let's get to it.
Shall we design and paint?
Yes!
What color should I do?
I don't know what color to choose.
It's different from the last time I did a coloring book.
Different...
No, no, no, no, no...I'll see you soon
Original.
Awesome body, hood, mirrors, wings,
Wheels, wheels, brakes, windows...
Isn't it amazing?
You can change everything.
Wow, that's extravagant.
I don't know what to do.
Let's start with the body.
There are so many colors to choose from!
Can we change the wheels too?
Yellow is cute too!
This is so fun!
I'm thinking of getting a pink one, but he can go home again.
I've been designing a new one for a while now, and I'm thinking of going with a pink one too.
I've been working on a design for a while now and I've been working on a design for a while now and I've been working on a design for a while now.
I'm going to design a pink one.
Aluminum Ally matte now I've made it matte, the case is so cool!
I've got a steel Damascus, a wood dark camouflage.
I can change the key, the brake, the brake, the brake...
It's so much cooler than having it done in steel.
If we, who are not so familiar with cars, are so excited about this, it means that if you really like cars, you must be crazy about them.
I'm sure you're right.
You can adjust the color by yourself, by pressing this X, and you can adjust the hue.
What? How do you do that?
You can adjust the hue of the color, like hue, side.
Wow.
Wow, glossy makeup is cool. Wow, that's some cool glossy makeup.
You've got to hurry up, you don't have time.
I'm going to put up a lot of things that I don't have time for.
Oh man, I don't have enough time for this.
Wow, there are letters and all kinds of things that are crazy.
Wow, what should I do?
I don't know what to do.
Cool, it looks like this star.
It would be cool if it were steel glossy.
Wow, I can't decide between yellow and blue. If I change the windows to pink, it's a bit weird.
Can you even change the color of the windows? You can even change the color of the windows.
Mirror. I don't know what to do with the mirror.
It's cool. And once we're done, we'll give you a notice.
What are you doing now? Yuuno is putting designs on cars.
It's nice. Putting up vinyls.
I think I'm going to go put decals on it too.
Brakes?
Still changing the color. You keep changing the color.
Oh, no, no, no. I have to put the logo on soon. This time,
I have to do it this time. It's difficult, you know.
It takes time. I'm going back.
I'm glad to see the color I used before. It's great.
I really appreciate that the position can be easily adjusted.
That's great. What should I do? I was so worried about the color until just now.
Oh, no. There are so many kinds of letters. There are so many kinds of letters. Where are the letters?
If you keep pressing RB, you'll find a lot of them. We're running out of time.
Is it OK to come here and see white?
Back to back. Let's try to make it burn up a little.
It's hard. Oh, cool.
Wow, it's so dark.Wow, so dark.
I finally cracked one.
Let's put something a little patterned in there, one time, for now.
There are so many!
There's too many!
Five more minutes?
Come on!
Sorry, we're running out of time.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
Let's make it a little bigger and more patterned.
Okay.
Let's just wave the flag.
For now...
So...
Cute!
This one too.
You know what?
If this is for a girl, it's just like a nudge.
You're right, you're right.
I want the logo
This time I want to put Mayama
Mayama
I want to put Mayama
Thank you for watching
Here are the three's completed cars.
I'm going to start with you first, how do you like it?
I'll start with you... and the ring... and since it's already pink, will you be nice to it?
I went with a car, but I'll leave the rest to you First of all, there are a lot of custom colors, and it looks like a lot of stamps
There are so many custom colors and stamps, and there are so many different kinds of stamps, so I was confused and thought it would be nice to see a cute white car running on the course from behind.
I decided to design the door and the back of the car with my attendance number, 07, rather than the front.I designed the doors and the back of the car with my attendance number, 07, rather than the front, and I didn't make it 007, because I lost heart on the way to 007.
What is the title of your car?
What's the title of your car?
I think it's still a very nice car, and I'm sure you'll be able to see it.
I think it's so nice.
I'm sure you'll be able to choose the color of the car.
Like that white star on the side.
I've already seen it. You can take it off.
You can see it when you look at it.
But it's quite stylish, isn't it?
You're quite stylish, Yuno.
Yuno is the most mature.
It's austere, but...
The small size of the letters
So that the viewer can see what it says.
It's a car with small letters to distract the viewer.
It's covered with stars from above.
It's a cool car.
It's really a star from the top.
It's nice.
It's full of stars.
So what's the title of this car?
It's called "The Distraction Car.
It's true, I might pay attention to it.
I'd like to draw attention to it.
It's the most likely one, and I want to drive it.
If I were to drive it, I would like to drive it.
Mr. Moe.
Yes, me?Yes, sir. Is it me?
May I go ahead and announce the title for a moment?
The title of this piece is "Gala.
Oh, my God.
All over the place.
Patterned.
Front, back, left, right.
Front, back, left, right, left, right.
That's the kind of distraction you'd expect in a high-end car.
You can't help but be curious about this car.
What's this?
I'd look right next to it.
I'd look right next to it. What?
I put the logo, "Logo Mayama" on the back.
I spent a lot of time putting it in.
So I decided to put a lot of different patterns on it.
Sure, we can enlarge them and fill them in.
I put a lot of patterns on it.
I'm surprised at myself.
It's funny, because Moemon and I are much older than we are, but Yuuno is the most reluctant of the two.
Yuuno was the most reluctant one.
Indeed.
That's for sure.
That's right.
She's the most childish.
Like a child's coloring book.
I did whatever I wanted.
I was free to do as I pleased.
Next time, I'd like to challenge a race with this car.Well, I'm going to try my hand at racing with this car next time!
Please check it out!
Enjoy!